<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- 护盾 -->
  <Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_I.label>Energy Shield - Stone Age</Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_I.label>
  <Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_I.description>The first game of the old generation Energy Shield is also the basis for subsequent works. There is no ability to recover, but the cost is low, and it can be easily installed \nFrom people lifting the first stone, to gods ruling everything, millions of years, people through their own strength, defeated countless beasts, established their own civilization, maybe all this is just a coincidence, but under the accumulation of countless coincidences, people through their own efforts, became the hegemon of the planet. Over such a long period of time, people learned to communicate quickly and make better use of the power of the team, which made them stand up.</Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_I.description>
  <Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_II.label>Energy Shield - Middle Ages</Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_II.label>
  <Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_II.description>The second game of the old generation of energy shields, only weak recovery ability and a very low energy ceiling, but low cost, easy to install\nFrom people blindly believing in gods, to discovering the greatness of people, a thousand years, in countless oppressions, people learned to work to create wealth, since then the gods have been pulled down from high positions, people create everything through their own hands, people have embarked on a right path, and since then science and technology have developed rapidly.</Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_II.description>
  <Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_III.label>Energy Shield - Industrial Age</Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_III.label>
  <Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_III.description>The third game of the old generation energy shield can withstand damage well, but it is not suitable for mass installation(?) \nInformation is erased</Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_III.description>
  <Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_IV.label>The fourth game of the old generation energy shield, can be energy shield - space age</Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_IV.label>
  <Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_IV.description>The fourth game of the old generation Energy Shield has a strong recovery ability and can resist a large amount of damage in a short time, but the cost is very high, and the market is less circulating\nInformation is deleted</Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_IV.description>
  <Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_V.label>Energy Shield - The Age of Ultra</Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_V.label>
  <Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_V.description>The fifth game of the old generation Energy Shield has a strong recovery ability and can resist a large amount of damage in a short time, but the cost is very high, and there is less circulation in the market\nInformation is erased</Apparel_Ling_OldWorld_V.description>
</LanguageData>
